wweallstars.com 2011-06-05

# THQ - Privacy policy

  1. Introduction
  2. What does this Privacy Policy apply to?
  3. What types of information does THQ collect?
  4. How does THQ use the information it collects?
  5. What happens if I refuse to provide my personal information to THQ?
  6. Does THQ use cookies, track IP addresses, or use other passive means to collect information?
  7. Who is collecting my personal information and is it shared with anyone?
  8. Can I choose how my personal information is used?
  9. How can I access my personal information?
  10. What is THQ's policy regarding children under 13?
  11. What safeguards does THQ use to protect my personal information?
  12. How do I ask a question or file a complaint? (Contact Information)
  13. Kids' Privacy Policy

* * *

### 1\. Introduction

THQ Inc. and its subsidiaries and affiliates (collectively "THQ" or "we") respect the privacy rights of our online visitors and are committed to protecting the personal information collected about you. To further this commitment, we have adopted this Online Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") to guide how we collect, store, and use the information you provide us online.

This Privacy Statement and the certification seal located on this page confirm that THQ is a valid licensee and participating member in the [Entertainment Software Rating Board's Privacy Online Program: ESRB Privacy Online](http://www.esrb.org/). To protect your privacy, we have voluntarily undertaken this privacy initiative and all of our websites have been reviewed and certified by ESRB Privacy Online to meet established online information collection and use practices. As part of this privacy program, we are subject to frequent audits of our sites and other enforcement and accountability mechanisms administered independently by ESRB Privacy Online.

Because the website you are currently visiting displays the ESRB Privacy Online certification seal, you can expect to be notified of the following.

**The scope of this Privacy Policy**

  * Exactly what information THQ may collect from you through its website(s)
  * How THQ will use the information it collects
  * What are the consequences if you refuse to divulge your personal information
  * Whether THQ uses cookies or other passive collection tools on its website(s)
  * Who collects the information that you disclose on a THQ website
  * With whom, if anyone, does THQ share your personal information

**What choices you can make regarding how your personal information is used**

  * How you can change or delete the information THQ has collected about you
  * What is THQ's policy regarding collecting information from children under 13
  * How THQ ensures the security, quality, and integrity of your information
  * How you can ask a question or file a complaint regarding this Privacy Policy

Back to top »

* * *

### 2\. What does this Privacy Policy apply to?

The website you are currently visiting is operated by THQ located at 29903 Agoura Road, Agoura Hills, CA 91301. This Privacy Policy currently applies to the website(s) operated by THQ (collectively referred to as "THQ Websites" or "our Websites"). Please [click here](http://www.thq.com/legal/notices.php) to see a complete list of the products that are featured on the THQ Websites. In the future, if we wish to include additional websites under this Privacy Policy, we will take reasonable steps to include them in the list and ensure that they provide a link to this Privacy Policy

Please note that this Privacy Policy applies only to information submitted and collected online through the THQ Websites (as listed above), and does _not_ apply to information that may be collected by THQ offline. In addition, this Privacy Policy does _not_ extend to websites maintained by our international affiliates (e.g., THQ Australia, THQ UK, THQ France, etc.) or other companies or organizations to which we link. Because we cannot guarantee that the privacy policies of such sites meet the requirements of the ESRB Privacy Online Program, we encourage you to read the privacy policy of the website to which you link before you submit any personal information to that site.

_Please note that by using our Websites, you signify your assent to THQ's Online Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use our Websites. We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy. _If we make a material change to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting the change on our Websites or in this Privacy Policy and, if necessary, give you additional choices regarding such change_. Please check back from time to time to ensure that you are aware of these changes. Your continued use of our Websites will signify your acceptance of these changes._

Back to top »

* * *

### 3\. What types of information does THQ collect?

In order to give you the best experience on our Websites, THQ may collect information about you, but only if you voluntarily provide it to us. Typically, we may ask you to submit personal and/or demographic information in connection with any one of the following features or services.

  * Website and game-specific registration 
  * Newsletter subscription 
  * General support 
  * Product support 
  * Online store 
  * Contests, sweepstakes, and other promotions 
  * Polls, surveys, or questionnaires 
  * Message boards 
  * Community websites and features
  * Other features such as e-cards, wish lists, and tell-a-friend* 

The types and amount of personal information collected for these activities will vary depending on the activity. The requested personal information may include: your name, home address, telephone number, e-mail address, Xbox Live Gamertag and/or PlayStation Network ID and (for those purchasing products online) credit card information including billing and shipping addresses. For some activities, we may ask you to create a username and password and to provide other non-personal information such as your age or date of birth, gender, game and platform preferences (including information about the games and hardware you own), hobbies and interests, and other information (also known as "demographic information"). If demographic information is collected for an activity that also requires personal information, we may combine the demographic information with your personal information. Combining data allows us to customize the notices we send you and the services we provide you according to your interests and preferences. Please note, when demographic information, or any other non-personal information, is combined with personal information, we shall treat all of the information, collectively, as personal information. For more on how we use your information, please read the section on use below.

* _Any email addresses collected from you during the use of the "Send to a Friend" or "Tell-A-Friend" feature on any THQ Website are not retained by THQ, and are only used to send a one-time email notification on your behalf._

No matter what method we use to collect information and no matter how we use that information, we will only collect the information deemed reasonably necessary to fulfill your online requests and our legitimate business objectives.

Back to top »

* * *

### 4\. How does THQ use the information it collects?

Generally, information that we collect for a particular purpose is used for that purpose only. For example, if you request product support, the email address that you provide will only be used for purposes of diagnosing your specific technical problem and providing an acceptable solution. Information collected from those who register on our Websites is used to provide registrants the benefits associated with such registration (e.g., subscription to newsletter or access to the latest game news and exclusive store promotions). And, of course, any credit card information is solely used to fulfill and process purchase orders. In some instances, however, you may also be given the option to have your information used for an activity or service different from the activity or service that you are requesting (e.g., to have your name entered into a contest when subscribing to our newsletter or vice versa). If you choose to receive these additional services, THQ will use your information to provide them to you.

We may use your email address to send you service-related announcements that tell you about updates to our Privacy Policy, new areas or features on our Websites, changes to our online service or technical support policies, and other related changes.

We may also use your personal and demographic information for our internal marketing and demographic studies, so we can constantly improve the online products and services we provide you and to better meet your needs.

Please be advised that in some areas of our Websites, you may be able to submit information about yourself in a business capacity. Although we can assure you that any personal information gathered in this context will be used solely for its intended purpose, such information is not subject to this Privacy Policy. These areas typically include an employment section where you can submit your resume online and/or an investors relations section where you can fill out an online form to request financial information about THQ.

Back to top »

* * *

### 5\. What happens if I refuse to provide my personal information to THQ?

If you choose not to submit personal information when requested, you may not be able to participate in certain activities on our Websites and may limit the services we can provide you. For example, if you refuse to share your email address, you may not be able to receive general support or product support. To simply browse our Websites, however, you do not need to give us any personal information.

Back to top »

* * *

### 6\. Does THQ use cookies, track IP addresses, or use other passive means to collect information?

The various means described below shall be collectively referred to as "Technical Methods."

### Cookies

We may use cookies to improve the use and functionality of our Websites. A "cookie" is a small file or record-keeping device that websites often store on a user's computer. Storage of cookies on your system provides an easy and convenient method for us to personalize your experience on our Websites. For example, cookies will remember what you've placed in your shopping cart, tell us that you have visited one of our Websites before, and may contain other information that will make your next visit to our Websites more enjoyable. We may combine information contained in cookies with your personal information. You can always disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent to your computer, although this may affect your ability to shop online, both at THQ and elsewhere.

### Web Beacons

We may use web beacons (or clear GIFs) on our Websites or include them in the e-mail messages we send you. Web beacons (also known as "web bugs") are small strings of code that provide a method of delivering a graphic image on a web page or in an email message for the purpose of transferring data. We use web beacons for many purposes, including site traffic reporting, unique visitor counts, advertising and email auditing and reporting, and personalization. Information gathered through web beacons may be linked to your personal information.

### IP Addresses

THQ may also keep track of Internet Protocol (IP) addresses to troubleshoot technical concerns and to maintain website safety and security. An IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer every time you log on to the Internet.

### Log Files

THQ may collect information in the form of logs - files that record website activity and gather statistics about web users' browsing habits. These entries are generated anonymously, and help THQ determine (among other things) how many and how often users have visited our Websites, which pages they've visited, and other similar data (a.k.a., navigational data). We also use the log file entries for our internal marketing and demographic studies, so we can constantly improve the online services we provide you. Log files are used internally only, and are not associated with any particular user, computer, or browser.

### Authentication

THQ may implement security measures from time to time in ensure that participants on our Websites and for services offered via the Websites are individuals rather than web crawlers, bots, or other automated programs. These authentication measures ensure a smooth and safe user experience.

Back to top »

* * *

### 7\. Who is collecting my personal information and is it shared with anyone?

The information that you disclose on the THQ Websites is collected by THQ or by a vendor on THQ's behalf; and, is used in accordance with the practices set forth above. Vendors (or agents) are entities that provide support for the internal operations of our Websites and who only use the information we share with them (or that they collect on our behalf) for purposes of internal fulfillment (e.g., online product fulfillment). Vendors are required to handle such information in accordance terms no less strict than those set forth in this Privacy Policy.

From time to time, we may run contests, tournaments, or other events or activities ("Events") on our Websites. Information collected for these Events may include personal information such as your email address and may be collected by or shared with a third party sponsor, co-sponsor, or other reputable third party (e.g., promotional partner, software licensee, or game developer). While we have no control over the third party's use of such information, we use reasonable efforts to always contractually ensure that they agree to protect the confidentiality, security, and integrity of any personal information we share with them (or that they collect through our Websites). If you do not want your information to be collected by or shared with a third party, you can choose not to participate in these Events at the time the information is collected 

We may disclose personal information in the good faith belief that we are required to do so by law, including but not limited to disclosure to law enforcement or other government officials in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose you or us to legal liability. In addition, in the event of a merger, acquisition, reorganization, bankruptcy, or other similar event, THQ's customer information may be transferred to our successor or assign.

Back to top »

* * *

### 8\. Can I choose how my personal information is used?

If you do not want to receive our newsletter, service related announcements, or any other communications and/or services from THQ, please opt-out from these communications or services at the time of registration or information collection. If you have opted-in and, at a later time, wish to opt-out, please visit the appropriate "Profile" section on our Websites or contact us using the information provided below.

### Your California Privacy Rights

Since 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits our customers who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. For inquiries regarding our disclosure policy, please contact us using the information provided below:

THQ Inc.  
29903 Agoura Road  
Agoura Hills, CA 91301.  

Back to top »

* * *

### 9\. How can I access my personal information?

If you wish to review, update, or delete any personal information that we may have collected about you, please visit the appropriate "Profile" section on our Websites or contact us using the information provided below.

Back to top »

* * *

### 10\. What is THQ's policy regarding children under 13?

We recognize the need to provide additional information and protections for those THQ Websites that are targeted to children under the age of 13, specifically the PlayTHQ Websites. To read our privacy policy specific to children under the age of 13, and the PlayTHQ Websites, please see our Kids' Privacy Policy below.

Please note, that from time to time, certain portions of the THQ Websites may allow children under 13 to disclose a limited amount of personal information without first telling us their age or getting their parent's permission. Such portions of our Websites operate activities or provide services in a way that does not require prior parental consent.

Back to top »

* * *

### 11\. What safeguards does THQ use to protect my personal information?

THQ takes reasonable measures to protect the confidentiality, security, and integrity of the personal information collected from our website visitors. Personal information collected by THQ is stored in secure operating environments that are not available to the public and that are only accessible to authorized employees. In addition, our online store uses industry-standard encryption to prevent unauthorized electronic access to sensitive financial information such as your credit card number. We also have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. For example, before we allow web users to access their personal information, we verify their identity by requesting information such as their username and password.

Although we cannot guarantee that third parties to whom we transfer personal data will adhere to the security standards set forth above, we will take reasonable measures, such as contractual obligations, to assure that they provide sufficient protection over such data.

Back to top »

* * *

### 12\. How do I ask a question or file a complaint? (Contact Information)

If you have any questions, complaints, or comments regarding this Privacy Policy or our information collection practices, please contact our Privacy Policy Administrator at:

THQ Inc.  
29903 Agoura Road  
Agoura Hills, CA 91301  

You can also contact ESRB Privacy Online directly at <http://www.esrb.org/privacy/contact.jsp> or at:

ESRB Privacy Online  
Attn.: Director, Privacy Online  
317 Madison Avenue, 22nd Floor  
New York, NY 10017  

This Privacy Policy was last updated on July 8, 2010.

Back to top »

* * *

### 13\. Kids' Privacy Policy

Building on our general Privacy Policy, THQ recognizes the need to provide additional privacy protections when children under the age of 13 visit the PlayTHQ Websites. Our Kids’ Privacy Policy describes how we collect and use personal information collected online from children. It also describes how parents can review the personal information that we have collected

For your convenience, the Kids’ Privacy Policy uses terms that are defined in our general Privacy Policy, shown above. A link to our privacy policies is also posted at the bottom of each THQ and PlayTHQ Website. 

### Collection, Use, and Disclosure of Information

We allow children to surf the PlayTHQ Websites, look at content, and play some games without giving us any personally identifiable information. We do not collect personal information from children unless they register on one of the PlayTHQ Websites for access to exclusive content and to receive newsletters regarding upcoming PlayTHQ videogame releases.

During registration for the PlayTHQ Websites, THQ requests and collects from children their e-mail address and birth date, a parent's e-mail address, and a member/user name. Birth dates are collected to validate the ages of our users, including children, and we collect a parent’s e-mail address to let parents know that their child has signed up with the PlayTHQ Websites, to verify their consent and send future notices about their child’s account. We also collect the child’s e-mail address for the purpose of sending the child e-mail related to their subscription to the PlayTHQ Websites and newsletters as mentioned above. We ask that parents set their child’s password, so that the parent has access to their child’s account and personally identifiable information at all times. This password can easily be retrieved or modified by a parent at any time using instructions provided below.

Please note that any sites directed at children under 13 are prohibited by law from conditioning a child's participation in an online activity on the child's providing more personal information than is reasonably necessary.

THQ does not sell, market, trade, or otherwise distribute personally identifiable information to third parties outside of our company. We will not use any of the information we collect from any registrant of the PlayTHQ Websites for any purpose other than to access the website, e-mailings as described above and for the purposes of contacting the parent. Situations in which we may share a child's personal information with third parties would include those in which it is reasonably necessary to: protect the security of integrity of the PlayTHQ Websites; to take precautions against liability; to respond to judicial process; or to the extent permitted under provisions of law, to provide information to law enforcement agencies, or for an investigation related to public safety.

For additional information about how THQ safeguards the personal information of its members please see our general Privacy Policy above.

### Electronic Postcards

All electronic postcards accessible on the PlayTHQ Websites request that users furnish an e-mail address. This is necessary to send the postcards electronically. The e-mail addresses are deleted from our servers and not distributed to third parties or used for any other purposes than sending the postcards.

### Technical Methods

If a parent allows their child to register with the PlayTHQ Websites and for us to collect personal information about their child, we may link certain Technical Methods to that personal information. These Technical Methods allow us to operate the PlayTHQ Websites more effectively, make them more interesting and useful to you and are beneficial for various purposes related to our business. We do not however collect any additional personally identifiable information via these Technical Methods. For further information about the particular Technical Methods used on the PlayTHQ Websites, please see our general Privacy Policy under the sub-heading: "Does THQ use cookies, track IP addresses, or use other passive means to collect information?"

### Sweepstakes and Contests

We send parents an e-mail when their child registers to enter a sweepstakes or contest on one of the PlayTHQ Websites. We provide parents 48 hours to confirm their child's registration and entry in the sweepstakes or contest. If a parent does not confirm their child’s registration request in this timeframe, we assume it is not acceptable for the child to enter the sweepstakes or contest, and we will delete their child’s information from our database of entries. Once a parent permits a child to register, the child will be allowed to complete their entry into the sweepstakes or contest. Only enough information as is required to enroll in the sweepstakes or contest will be collected. After the drawing or contest is concluded, we will not retain any additional personally identifiable information collected beyond the information already provided at the time of registration for the PlayTHQ Websites. If a child wins a sweepstakes or contest, we notify the parent at the parent's e-mail address provided to us during the registration process and request that the parent provide their postal address for purposes of delivering the prize. We may publish a winner's first name, first initial of last name, city, and state of residence on the PlayTHQ Websites.

### Parental Consent

We require that parents give us express permission for their child to register with the PlayTHQ Websites. Additionally, at any time parents can refuse to permit us to collect further personal information from their child and can request that any personal information we have collected be deleted from our database. The parent will need to have their child's member name and password. If the password has been lost or forgotten, there are instructions on the PlayTHQ Account Maintenance for Parents page explaining how to recover or set a new password for access. There are three methods for a parent to access, change, or delete the personally identifiable information that we have collected from their children:

  1. Using the e-mail first sent to them by THQ, a parent can click on the link provided to take them to the PlayTHQ Account Maintenance for Parents page. Once linked to this page a parent will be able to log in to their child’s account, review, change or delete any of their child’s personal information, as well as update their child’s password.
  2. A parent can access their child's account information using the following link: <http://www.playthq.com/myplaythq/parental_maintenance.php>, which will direct them to the PlayTHQ Account Maintenance for Parents page. Once linked to this page, a parent can log in to their child’s account, review, change or delete any of their child’s personal information, as well as update their child’s password.
  3. A parent can also visit www.PlayTHQ.com. By clicking the link at the top of the home page entitled "For Parents" they will be provided with informative text. A link to the PlayTHQ Account Maintenance for Parents page is provided under the subheading "How can I review, modify or delete my child’s PlayTHQ registration information?" By following the link, a parent will be able to use their child’s information to review, change or delete any of their child’s personal information as well as update their child’s password.

### Links to Other Sites

When children click on links from the PlayTHQ Websites to other sites, we may open the other sites in a new browser window. We make every effort to only link the PlayTHQ Websites to appropriate outside sites for children, and will advise a user when leaving the PlayTHQ Websites. Unlike the PlayTHQ Websites, however, these outside sites may collect personal information, which is outside of the control of THQ.

### Amendments to this Policy

We may amend our Kids' Privacy Policy at any time. We will provide parents notice by e-mail in the event of any material changes in the way we intend to collect, use, and/or share a child’s personal information. Please note that, at all times, parents should keep their personal information updated and provide us with current e-mail addresses. THQ will only apply material changes to the Kids' Privacy Policy in conformance with applicable law, including any applicable provisions of the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act that require parental consent.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Kids’ Privacy Policy or our information collection practices, please contact our Privacy Policy Administrator at:

THQ Inc.  
29903 Agoura Road  
Agoura Hills, CA 91301  
(818) 871-5000  
Fax: (818) 871-7400  

You can also contact ESRB Privacy Online directly at <http://www.esrb.org/privacy/contact.jsp> or at:

ESRB Privacy Online  
Attn.: Director, Privacy Online  
317 Madison Avenue, 22nd Floor  
New York, NY 10017  

This Kid’s Privacy Policy was last updated on June 9, 2008
